<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>research on Timm Lichte</title>
    <link>http://timm-lichte.de/tags/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in research on Timm Lichte</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 12:55:20 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://timm-lichte.de/tags/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://timm-lichte.de/publications/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 12:55:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://timm-lichte.de/publications/publications/</guid>
      <description>The used citation style is the Unified Style Sheet for Linguistics.
\(\rightarrow\) CSL, BibLaTeX, support for Jabref and Papercite, plain-text converter
To appear Lichte, Timm. To appear. Against strict headedness in syntax. Journal of Language Modelling.
2020 Carlos Ramisch, Agata Savary, Bruno Guillaume, Jakub Waszczuk, Marie Candito, Ashwini Vaidya, Verginica Barbu Mititelu, Archna Bhatia, Uxoa Iñurrieta, Voula Giouli, Tunga Gungor, Menghan Jiang, Timm Lichte, Chaya Liebeskind, Johanna Monti, Renata Ramisch, Sara Stymne, Abigail Walsh, Hongzhi Xu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://timm-lichte.de/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 22:56:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://timm-lichte.de/about/about/</guid>
      <description>As of September 2018, I&amp;rsquo;m coordinator of the Department of Computer Science at the University of Tübingen. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m furthermore filling a substitute professorship (50%) on &amp;ldquo;Applied Computational Linguistics&amp;rdquo; at the University of Bielefeld.
Before that, I was postdoc researcher and principal investigator in project A02 of the CRC991 at the University of Düsseldorf. Before that, I did my PhD within Laura Kallmeyer’s Emmy Noether project at the University of Tübingen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software &amp; Resources</title>
      <link>http://timm-lichte.de/software/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 17:57:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://timm-lichte.de/software/software/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved in the creation of the following software and resources.
Language resources  COLF-VID: Corpus of Literal and Figurative Readings PARSEME Shared Task: Corpus of German idioms  Grammar engineering  XMG-WebGUI: A web GUI for compiling and displaying metagrammars written with XMG. TuLiPA: A parsing environment for variants of Tree-Adjoining Grammar.  LaTeX  LaTeX templates Langscibook class: The book template of Language Science Press.  Emacs  org-fm: Fast minutes with org-fm  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>http://timm-lichte.de/events/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 17:53:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://timm-lichte.de/events/events/</guid>
      <description>Talks &amp;amp; Presentations Timm Lichte. 2018. Incremental inference-based MWE processing with TUCO. Talk at Cognitive Structures: Linguistic, Philosophical and Psychological Perspectives (CoSt 2018). 12.–14. September 2018, Düsseldorf.
Timm Lichte &amp;amp; Christian Wurm. 2018. Meaning and Combinatorics of Ambiguity. Poster at the Ambigo Workshop, 4.–6. July 2018, University of Göttingen.
Fabienne Cap, Rafael Ehren, Maximilian Köper, Timm Lichte, Sabine Schulte im Walde &amp;amp; Heike Zinsmeister. 2018. VerbCompoCor: A German Corpus with Compositionality Judgments for Verb-Dependent Pairs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
