<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>research on Timm Lichte</title>
    <link>http://timm-lichte.de/tags/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in research on Timm Lichte</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://timm-lichte.de/tags/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://timm-lichte.de/publications/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://timm-lichte.de/publications/publications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;to-appear&#34;&gt;To appear&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lichte, Timm. To appear. Against strict headedness in syntax. Journal of Language Modelling.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poster session at DGfS 2022</title>
      <link>http://timm-lichte.de/posts/poster-session-dgfs-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://timm-lichte.de/posts/poster-session-dgfs-2022/</guid>
      <description>Together with Rainer Osswald, I am organizing the computational linguistics poster session at the 44th annual meeting of the German Linguistic Society (DGfS) in Tübingen which will be held online. The poster session is organized by the Special Interest Group on Computational Linguistics of the DGfS.
The call for abstracts can be found here: https://uni-tuebingen.de/de/220206
Note that the deadline for submissions is November 23, 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://timm-lichte.de/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 09:52:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://timm-lichte.de/about/about/</guid>
      <description>As of September 2018, I&amp;rsquo;m coordinator of the Department of Computer Science at the University of Tübingen.
Before that, I was postdoc researcher and principal investigator in project A02 of the CRC991 at the University of Düsseldorf. Before that, I did my PhD within Laura Kallmeyer’s Emmy Noether project at the University of Tübingen. Before that I had been studying General Linguistics, Rhetorics and Computer Science in Tübingen and Berlin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software &amp; Resources</title>
      <link>http://timm-lichte.de/software/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 17:57:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://timm-lichte.de/software/software/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved in the creation of the following software and resources.
Language resources  COLF-VID: Corpus of Literal and Figurative Readings PARSEME Shared Task: Corpus of German idioms  Grammar engineering  XMG-WebGUI: A web GUI for compiling and displaying metagrammars written with XMG. TuLiPA: A parsing environment for variants of Tree-Adjoining Grammar.  LaTeX  LaTeX templates Langscibook class: The book template of Language Science Press.  Emacs  org-fm: Fast minutes with org-fm  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>http://timm-lichte.de/events/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 17:53:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://timm-lichte.de/events/events/</guid>
      <description>Talks &amp;amp; Presentations Timm Lichte. 2018. Incremental inference-based MWE processing with TUCO. Talk at Cognitive Structures: Linguistic, Philosophical and Psychological Perspectives (CoSt 2018). 12.–14. September 2018, Düsseldorf.
Timm Lichte &amp;amp; Christian Wurm. 2018. Meaning and Combinatorics of Ambiguity. Poster at the Ambigo Workshop, 4.–6. July 2018, University of Göttingen.
Fabienne Cap, Rafael Ehren, Maximilian Köper, Timm Lichte, Sabine Schulte im Walde &amp;amp; Heike Zinsmeister. 2018. VerbCompoCor: A German Corpus with Compositionality Judgments for Verb-Dependent Pairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shared Task at KONVENS 2021</title>
      <link>http://timm-lichte.de/posts/shared-task-konvens-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://timm-lichte.de/posts/shared-task-konvens-2021/</guid>
      <description>Together with Rafael Ehren, Kuba Waszczuk and Laura Kallmeyer, I&amp;rsquo;m currently organizing a shared task at KONVENS 2021 that aims at disambiguating literal and idiomatic occurrence of German verbal multi-word expressions, so-called verbal idioms (VIDs), in running text. An example would be the VID Das Konzert fiel ins Wasser (&amp;lsquo;The concert was canceled&amp;rsquo;) as opposed to literal counterparts such as Das Handy fiel ins Wasser (&amp;lsquo;The mobile phone fell into the water&amp;rsquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
